Register of the J. Arthur Duff papers
Hoover Institution Archives
J. Arthur Duff papers
1906-1996
85082
Duff, J. Arthur (James Arthur), 1899-1996.
14 manuscript boxes, 1 oversize box (6.8 linear feet)
Hoover Institution Archives Stanford, California 94305-6010
The papers relate to missionaries in China, political and social conditions in China before and during World War II and American intelligence operations in China during World War II.
Administrative Information
Access
Collection is open for research. Access to audiovisual materials requires at least two weeks advance notice. Audiovisual materials include sound recordings, video recordings, and motion picture film. Hoover staff will determine whether use copies of the materials requested can be made available. Some materials may not be accessible even with advance notice. Please contact the Hoover Institution Archives for further information.
Acquisition Information
Acquired by the Hoover Institution Archives in 1985
Accruals
Materials may have been added to the collection since this finding aid was prepared. To determine if this has occurred, find the collection in Stanford University's online catalog Socrates at http://library.stanford.edu/webcat. Materials have been added to the collection if the number of boxes listed in Socrates is larger than the number of boxes listed in this finding aid.
Biographical Note
1899 November 14 Born in Kuling, China
1911-1920 Sent to live with relatives in Ontario, Canada
1920 Returned to China, went into business in Shanghai
1926 Married Jeanie Woodbridge (a China-born daughter of 13 generations of Canadian ministers and missionaries). They had five children: Woodrow, Virginia, Arthur, David, and Teddy
1939 J. Arthur Duff moved his family to the United States when the Japanese invaded China
1941 December-1942 February Escaped internment in Hong Kong
1942 Recruited by the O.S.S. and returned to China to operate as an O.S.S. agent on the Chinese mainland for the duration of the war
1945-1960 Established a highly successful manufacturing and retail business in several areas in the Far East
1960 Retired from active business becoming a world-wide wanderer
1979 Had a stroke
1990 Suffered a series of strokes, entered a nursing facility at Carewest Calistoga, California
1996 August 2 Died, California
Scope and Content of Collection
The papers relate to missionaries in China, political and social conditions in China before and during World War II and American intelligence operations in China during World War II.
Biographical file includes personal documents of and about J. Arthur Duff, as well as information on his wife, Mrs. Jeannie Woodbridge-Duff. The biographical file also includes documentation on Duff's positions in private business. A substantial part of the collection contains material on Duff's escape from Hong Kong, his return to China, and work for the OSS. In early spring of 1942, Cornelius V. Starr established an ambitious intelligence plan called "The Counter Japanese Division of COI." His insurance company and newspapers were to be used as cover to collect intelligence in China. Duff joined this group and led the counter-Japanese division in Chungking. His work provided significant documentation on the situation in the Pacific and in the China-Burma sector. Duff's performance, grasp of strategic issues, and persistence in upholding the course of action he believed to be viable is documented, as are his disagreements with C. V. Starr.
Correspondence contains business and personal documents, including extensive correspondence and the collected writings of Barbara W. Tuchman, an authority on the subject of Joseph W. Stilwell's life and career.
Typewritten memoirs constitute the most significant segment of the Writings series. Therein Duff recorded details of his daily life, his thoughts on various subjects, his trips, and his personal life. According to his daughter Virginia Black, his lack of training or knowledge in a subject area did not impose any restraints or restrictions whatsoever on his outspoken opinion. This series is divided into three parts by the time of the event, topic, and miscellany writings on various issues (See J. Arthur Duff papers, Box 1, Folder 1).
Background material consists of materials by other authors, generally similar in topic to his own work, such as childhood memoirs, China and its people, customs and culture, World War II, and world's current events issues. It also includes photocopies of books and articles, press summaries, studies, reports, clippings, and printed materials related to the subject of his interests.
Finally, the Photographs depict scenes and people from China, Canada, Africa, and many places of the United States. Also included are an extensive amount of prints documenting Duff family members and their travels around the world.
Indexing Terms
The following terms have been used to index the description of this collection in the library's online public access catalog.
United States. Office of Strategic Services; Burma-History-Japanese occupation, 1942-1945; China-History-Republic, 1912-1949; China-Social conditions; World War, 1939-1945-China; World War, 1939-1945-Campaign-Burma; World War, 1939-1945-Secret service; Secret service-United States; Canadians-China; Missions-China; Missionaries
Collection Contents
- Biographical file, 1942-1996; Boxes 1-2
  Personal documents and China claim documents.
  Arranged by physical form.
  - Biographical note written by his children, August 1996 (Folder 1: 1)
    Includes Duff family tree.
  - Family history, 1942-1943 (Folder 1: 2)
    Includes report on James A. Duff service in the OSS.
  - China claim documents, 1943-1984
    - Explanatory notes to claims, 1943 (Folder 1: 3-4)
    - American claims against Chinese-expropriated properties and businesses, 1970-1984 (Folder 1: 5-7)
    - British claims. Foreign Compensation Commission, London, 1981-1984 (Folder 1: 8-9)
    - Canadian claims. Foreign Claims Commission, Ottawa, 1981-1982 (Folder 1: 10-11)
  - Address/note books, 1950-1985 (Folder 1: 12-13)
  - Certificate of marriage, 1926 March 11 (Folder 1: 14)
  - Passports, 1943-1966 (Folder 1: 15-16)
  - Passports, 1943-1966 (Folder 2: 1)
  - Material on trip around the world, 1970-1972 (Folder 2: 2)
  - Articles about J. Arthur Duff, 1975-1984 (Folder 2: 3)
- Office of Strategic Services file, 1940-1985; Box 2
  Personal files, notes, remarks, memorandum, letters, and reports related to Duff's service in the counter-Japanese division in Chungking, China.
  Arranged chronologically by physical form.
  - History of service written in his own words, 1942-1943 (Folder 2: 4)
  - James A. Duff OSS confidential file, 1942-1981 (Folder 2: 5)
    Includes certificate of identification.
  - Materials related to Duff's OSS activities
    - OSS information relating to arrangements between Cornelius V. Starr and General Donovan. Memoirs are recollected in, 1983-1984 (Folder 2: 6)
      Includes clippings.
    - Notes and remarks on C. V. Starr, 1940-1984 (Folder 2: 7)
    - Headquarters Philippine Department, Office of Assistant Chief of Staff for Military Intelligence, Manila, 1938 December 14 (Folder 2: 8)
    - Memorandum and correspondence to executives of Starr Group regarding James A. Duff escape from Honk Kong, 1942 (Folder 2: 9)
    - Confidential letter from the Director of OSS William J. Donovan to former members of OSS, 1945 September 28. (Folder 2: 10)
      Includes information, letters translated from Chinese, and photographs of Yu Han Mou, 1944.
    - Memorandum issued by J. A. Duff regarding China (political, economical and cultural conditions), 1965 April 16 (Folder 2: 11)
    - Confidential memo regarding situation in Cuba, 1960 March 29 (Folder 2: 12)
    - Minutes of meeting with Higher Education Delegation from the People's Republic of China, 1985 January 30. (Folder 2: 13)
      Includes material on China's Reunification under the Three Principles of the People, Taipei, October 22, 1982.
  - Reports, 1941-1985
    - Simulated report of the Royal Commission headed by Sir Lyman P. Duff, Chief Justice, charged with an investigating the circumstances leading up to the dispatch of two Canadian regiments to the British crown colony of Hong Kong in, October-November 1941 (Folder 2: 14)
    - Incarceration of Japanese in Canada after Pearl Harbor, undated (Folder 2: 15)
    - Trip to Canton, 1957 October 4-7 (Folder 2: 16)
    - Intelligence and Sabbath observance. Includes comments on fundamental and modernity in religion, 1985 (Folder 2: 17)
    - Arab oil rip-off has destroyed the "American Way" in pricing, and competition: there may come a day of reckoning - a "Sonic Boom" which can destroy the entire basis of "Free Enterprise," and the financial system with it, circa 1985 (Folder 2: 18)
- Writings, 1942-circa 1985.; Boxes 2-6
  Memoirs/book notes, reviews, miscellaneous writings.
  Arranged chronologically or alphabetically by topic.
  - Memoirs/book notes, circa 1982-1985
    - Chronological writings' drafts
      - 1906-1910 (Childhood) (Folder 2: 19)
      - 1914 (Early days in Canada) (Folder 2: 20)
      - 1926-1927 (Events in Kuling-Kiukiang) (Folder 2: 21-22)
      - 1932 (Shanghai incidents) (Folder 2: 23)
      - 1934 (Japan occupied Manchuria) (Folder 2: 24)
      - 1937-1938 (Folder 2: 25)
      - 1939 (Folder 3: 1)
      - 1940 (Folder 3: 2)
      - 1941-1942 (Folder 3: 3)
      - 1943 (Folder 3: 4-7)
      - 1944 (Folder 3: 8)
      - 1946-1947 (Folder 3: 9)
      - 1971 (Folder 3: 10)
    - Topics
      - Beggars (Folder 3: 11)
      - Chinese currency (Folder 3: 12)
      - Chinese customs (Folder 3: 13)
      - Chinese characteristics (Folder 3: 14)
      - China coast characteristics
        - General (Folder 3: 15)
        - Sammy Chang (Folder 3: 16)
        - Mimi Lau (Folder 3: 17)
        - Chang-Tin-Chuk (Folder 3: 18)
        - Eugenia Moore, Honigsberg et Al (Folder 3: 19)
        - Oren B. Mctavish (Folder 3 :20)
      - Chungking: First Arrival by Plane (Folder 3 :21)
      - Compradores and chits (Folder 3: 22)
      - Converts (Folder 3: 23)
      - Count Igor (Folder 3: 24)
      - Devon (Folder 3: 25)
      - Escape From Hong Kong To Free China
        - Original typescript, 1942 (Folder 3: 26)
        - Newspaper articles, photograph, introduction to Hong Kong escape manuscript (Folder 3: 27)
        - Escape From Hong Kong To Free China, January and February, 1942, printed by the South China Morning Post, Limited, Hong Kong, undated (Folder 3: 28)
        - Hong Kong escape aftermath (Folder 4: 1)
        - Hong Kong: Post-war episodes (Folder 4: 2)
        - Photographs, maps, notes, and correspondence (Folder 4: 3)
      - Ernest Hemingway (Folder 4: 4)
      - Face (Folder 4: 5)
      - Fall of Hong Kong (Folder 4: 6)
      - Far Away and Long Ago, reminiscences of, 1899-1982 (Folder 4: 7)
      - General Morris "Two-Gun" Cohen (Folder 4: 8)
      - High finance in Shanghai (Folder 4: 9)
      - Hollis H. Arnold (Folder 4: 10)
      - Home leave (Folder 4: 11)
      - John Francis Duff (eldest brother) (Folder 4: 12)
      - Kiukiang/Kuling (Folder 4: 13)
      - Kiukiang: animal characteristics (Folder 4: 14)
      - Kuling (Folder 4: 15-16)
      - Language (Folder 4: 17)
      - Language of diplomacy (Folder 4: 18)
      - Loong Kai Ho Creek - Kiukiang (Folder 4: 19)
      - Lu Chat (Folder 4: 20)
      - Madame Chiang Kai Shek - And Her "Helpers" (Folder 4: 21)
      - Margaret Anne (Ostler) Duff, 1869-1952 (Mother) (Folder 4: 22)
      - Mary (Folder 4: 23)
      - Missionaries (Folder 4: 24)
      - Old China hands (Folder 4: 25)
      - On retirement (Folder 4: 26)
      - Opium (Folder 4: 27)
      - Religion (Folder 4: 28)
      - Return to Kiukiang (Folder 4: 29)
      - Sex in China (Folder 4: 30)
      - Shanghai (Folder 4: 31)
      - Shanghai volunteers (Folder 4: 32)
      - Squeeze (Folder 4: 33)
      - Story of Dr. Wassel (Folder 4: 34)
      - Street writers (Folder 4: 35)
      - Thieves in China (Folder 4: 36)
      - Three waterfalls (Folder 4: 37)
      - To follow General Chiang Kai-Shek and General Stilwell "Old China Hands" (Folder 4: 38)
      - Wartime notes (Folder 5: 1-2)
      - Water buffalo (Folder 5: 3)
    - Miscellaneous writings on current events, 1969-1985 (Folder 5: 4-10)
  - Reviews, 1960-1985
    - Comments on The Universe, undated (Folder 6: 1)
    - The Answer to "Peaceful Co-Existence,", June 1960. (Folder 6: 2)
    - Evolution or Special Creation, some notes and commentary on the book by Frank Lewis Marsh, 1963 (Folder 6: 3)
    - Comments on M19 Escape and Evasion: 1939-1945 by M. R. D. Foot and J. M. Langley, 1985 (Folder 6: 4)
    - Comments on newspaper articles, 1976 (Folder 6: 5)
    - Empire of the Sun, by J. G. Ballard (Folder 6: 6)
- Correspondence, 1889-1986.; Boxes 6-7
  Contains correspondence of both a business and personal nature.
  Arranged alphabetically by name of correspondent.
  - Personal letters, family correspondence, 1889-1985 (Folder 6: 7-11)
  - 1940 (Folder 6: 12)
  - 1942-1972. (Folder 6: 13)
    Includes one photograph and photographic negatives.
  - 1960-1979 (Folder 6: 14)
  - 1964 (Folder 6: 15)
  - 1976 (Folder 6: 16)
  - 1982-1984 (Folder 6: 17)
  - 1982-1985 (Folder 6: 18)
  - 1984 (Folder 6: 19)
  - 1984-1985 (Folder 6: 20-21)
  - 1985 (Folder 6: 22)
  - 1986 (Folder 6: 23)
  - Wilson, Edith Bolling, four letters, 1929 (Folder 6: 24)
  - Parker, George A., 1941. (Folder 6: 25)
    Includes photos and clippings, 1938-1943. Also includes life story of Lum-King-Hwen (in Chinese with English translation)
  - Lockwoods family, Kukong (China), 1942. (Folder 6: 26)
  - Soong-Ching-ling, Madame, letter to, 1962 (Folder 6: 27)
  - Sevareid, Eric (CBS News), 1965 (Folder 6: 28)
  - Tuchman, Barbara, 1975-1984. (Folder 6: 29)
  - Hoyles, W. F., 1976. (Folder 6: 30)
  - Munro, Ross H., 1977 (Folder 6: 31)
  - Wedemeyer, Albert, 1960-1985 (Folder 6: 32-33)
  - Wedemeyer, Albert, 1960-1985 (Folder 7: 1-2)
  - Miscellany, 1983-1984 (Folder 7: 3)
  - Envelopes addressed to Duff, 1939-1944 (Folder 7: 4)
  - Telegram receipts, 1930 (Folder 7: 5)
- Background material, 1912-1985; Boxes 7-12
  Consists of collected secondary sources which includes photocopies of books and articles, press summaries, studies, reports, clippings, and printed materials.
  Arranged by subject, and then sorted alphabetically by title
  - Books (photocopies), 1912-1981
    - Borodin: Stalin's Man in China, by Dan N. Jacobs, Harvard University Press, Cambridge, Massachusetts and London, England, 1981 (Folder 7: 6)
    - China in Revolution: The First Phase, 1900-1913, edited and with an introduction by Mary Clabaugh Wright. New Haven and London: Yale University Press, 1968 (Folder 7: 7)
    - The China Story, by Freda Utley, published by Henry Regnery Company, Chicago, 1951 (Folder 7: 8)
    - The Correspondence of G. E. Morrison, 1895-1912, edited by Lo Hui-Min, published by Cambridge University Press, Cambridge, London-New York-Melbourne, 1986-1978 (Folder 7: 9)
    - The Correspondence of G. E. Morrison, volume II, edited by Lo Hui-Min, Cambridge University Press, Cambridge, London-New York-Melbourne, 1978 (Folder 7: 10)
    - Darjeeling: Queen of the Himalayas, compiled by William G. Elloy. Produced by Daw Sen and Co. Private Ltd., Calcutta, 1960 (Folder 7: 11)
    - Donald of China, by Earl Albert Selle, published by Invincible Press, Sydney, Melbourne, Brisbane, Adelaide and New Zealand, 1938-1948. (Folder 7: 12)
      Includes extensive reviews and related articles, 1938-1948.
    - Ernest Hemingway and His World, by Anthony Burgess (photocopies of some parts). Published by Charles Scribner's Sons, New York, 1978 (Folder 7: 13)
    - The Exile, by Pearl S. Buck, published by Methuen and Co. Ltd., London, 1936-1956. (Folder 8: 1)
      (six editions)
    - The Face of War, by Martha Gellhorn, published by Simon and Schuster, New York, 1936-1959 (Folder 8: 2)
    - Fighting Angel: A Biography of the Author's Father, by Pearl S. Buck, published by The John Day Company, New York, 1936 (Folder 8: 3)
    - The Flying Tigers: The Story of the American Volunteer Group, by Russell Whelan, The Viking Press, New York, 1942. (Folder 8: 4)
      Includes The New York Times Book Review from November 1, 1942
    - Hill Resorts of India, issued on behalf of Department of Tourism, Government of India, New Delhi, 1961 (Folder 8: 5)
    - Hong Kong Eclipse, by G. B. Endacott. Edited with additional material by Alan Birch, Oxford University Press, Oxford-New York-Melbourne, 1978 (Folder 8: 6)
    - The Hump: The Great Military Affair of World War II, by Bliss K. Thorne, J.B. Lippincott Company, Philadelphia and New York, 1965 (Folder 8: 7)
    - I Flew For China, by Captain Royal Leonard (Chiang Kai-shek's personal pilot), published by Doubleday, Doran and Company, Inc., Garden City, New York, 1943 (Folder 8: 8)
    - Important Documents Relating to China's Revolution (With English Translation)), published by Commercial Press Limited, Shanghai, China, 1912 (Folder 8: 9)
    - The Islands: America's Imperial Adventure in the Philippines, by Emily Hahn, published by Coward, McCann and Geoghegan, New York, 1981 (Folder 8: 10)
    - Kuling Estate: Directory and general Information for Visitors, issued under the direction of the Kuling Council, 1925-1926 (Folder 8: 11)
    - Last Chance in China, by Freda Utley, published by the Bobbs-Merrill Company, Indianapolis-New York, 1947 (Folder 8: 12)
    - The Ledo Road: General Joseph W. Stilwell's Highway to China, by Leslie Anders, University of Oklahoma Press, 1965 (Folder 9: 1)
    - Odyssey of a Liberal: memoirs, by Freda Utley, excerpts. Published by Washington National Press, Inc., Washington, D.C., 1970. (Folder 9: 2)
      Includes letter of J. Arthur Duff to General (Wedemeyer?), October 1983.
    - "Rivershade": A Historical Sketch of Kiangyin Station, China, by Lacy L. Little, circa 1928 (Folder 9: 3)
    - The Soong Sisters, by Emily Hahn, published by Doubleday, Doran and Co., Inc., New York, 1941 (Folder 9: 4)
    - Suez to Singapore, Cecil Brown story, by Random House, Inc., published simultaneously in Canada by The Macmillan Company of Canada Limited, 1942. (Folder 9: 5)
      Includes note about Cecil Brown in Random House, New York.
    - The War of The Running Dogs: the Malayan Emergency: 1948-1960, by Noel Barber, published by Weybright and Talley, New York, 1972 (Folder 9: 6)
  - Books on the World War II (excerpts), 1969-1980
    - The War in the Far East 1941-1945: a Military History, by Basil Collier, published by William Morrow and Company, Inc., New York, 1969 (Folder 9: 7)
    - Stilwell and the Amrican Experience in China, 1911-1945, by Barbara W. Tuchman, published by The Macmillan Company, New York, 1970-1971 (Folder 9: 8)
    - The Chindit War: Stilwell, Wingate, and the Campaign in Burma: 1944, by Shelford Bidwell, with introduction by John Masters. Published by Macmillan Publishing Co., Inc., New York, 1980 (Folder 9: 9)
    - Singapore: The Chain of Disaster: A Controversial Account of Britain's Humiliation in the Far East, by Major-General S. Woodburn Kirby. Published by Macmillan Company, New York, 1971 (Folder 9: 10)
  - Clippings, mostly from The New York Times, 1912-1985
    - 1912-1938, 1976 (Folder 9: 11)
    - 1926-1927 (Folder 9: 12)
    - 1926-1927 (Folder 10: 1)
    - 1937 (Folder 10: 2)
    - 1937-1939 (Folder 10: 3)
    - 1937-1941 (Folder 10: 4)
    - 1938 (Folder 10: 5-6)
    - 1940 (Folder 10: 7)
    - 1941 (Folder 10: 8)
    - 1942, 1944 (Folder 10: 9)
    - 1945 (Folder 11: 1-4)
    - 1945, 1984 (Folder 11: 5)
    - 1946 (Folder 11: 6)
    - 1946, 1982 (Folder 11: 7)
    - 1946 1984 (Folder 11: 8)
    - 1949 (Folder 11: 9)
    - 1949-1951, 1960-1968, 1984 (Folder 11: 10)
    - 1977-1983 (Folder 11: 11)
    - 1978 (Folder 11: 12)
    - 1981-1982 (Folder 11: 13)
    - 1982-1983 (Folder 11: 14)
    - 1983 (Folder 12: 1)
    - 1983-1984 (Folder 12: 2-4)
    - 1984-1985 (Folder 12: 5)
- Jeannie Woodbridge (Mrs. J. Arthur Duff) file, 1921-1984; Boxes 12-13
  Includes documents of a personal nature.
  Arranged chronologically.
  - Notebook, 1921 (Folder 12: 6)
  - Correspondence, 1960-1984 (Folder 12: 7)
  - Driver's License, 1939-1982 (Folder 12: 8)
  - Passports
    - American, 1918-1961 (Folder 12: 9)
    - British, 1939 (Folder 12: 9)
  - Memoirs, undated. (Folder 12: 10-13)
    Includes original drafts and notes.
  - Photo copy of the book History of the American Field Service in France, 1914-1917, printed by Houghton Mifflin Company, Boston and New York, 1920 (Folder 12: 14-15)
  - Woodbridge family documents
    - General, 1917-1984 (Folder 13: 1)
    - Woodbridge Record, privately printed at New Haven, Connecticut, 1883 (Folder 13: 2)
  - Memorial service, conducted in Palo Alto, California, 1984 March 20 (Folder 13: 3)
- Photographs, 1905-1977; Boxes 13-14
  Prints depicting scenes and people from China, Canada, Africa, and many places of the United States. Includes prints documenting Duff family members. Also includes negatives.
  - Kuling pictures, undated (Folder 13: 4-5)
  - Portrait, undated (Folder 13: 6)
  - Views of China, undated (Folder 13: 7)
  - Duff family photo, 1905 (Folder 13: 8)
  - Jeannie Duff collection of family photographs, 1906-1934 (Folder 13: 9-11)
  - Kiukiang-Kuling area with comments, 1920s (Folder 13: 12)
  - Kiukiang-Kuling area, photo album, 1923-1939 (Folder 13: 13)
  - Various photos with notes to accompany pictures of China, and Duff family in China., 1926-1927. (Folder 13: 14-15)
    Pictures of China and of various China people and the Duff Kuling and Kiukiang properties follow are numbered.
  - Photographs of top Chinese Army Generals, 1926-1942 (Folder 13: 15)
  - Pictures of China with comments, 1926-1943 (Folder 13: 16)
  - Album of pictures depicting African and Chinese everyday life, 1932-1939 (Folder 14: 1)
  - Pictures of China with explanatory notes, 1934-1938 (Folder 14: 2)
  - Family photos, China, 1936-1937 (Folder 14: 3)
  - Cairo, Egypt, 1942 (Folder 14: 4)
  - Chang-tin-chuk (Chief of the Kwantung Bureau and Commissioner of the Commission on Overseas Affairs) and J. Arthur Duff in South China, 1943 (Folder 14: 5)
  - Lum-king-hwen (Lin) and Li-fuk-lum, 1943 (Folder 14: 6)
  - Picture and map of China giving the location of Taipun Bias Bay north of Hong Kong, 1944 (Folder 14: 7)
  - Picturesque photos of Duff family in Canada, 1946-1977. (Folder 14: 8)
    Includes pictures with Bert Chen.
  - J. Arthur Duff collection of photographs, photo copies of originals, 1900-1951 (Folder 14: 9)
  - Photograph folders with explanatory notes (Folder 14: 10-11)
  - Negatives, 1910-1943 and undated (Folder 14: 12)
- Oversize file, 1943-1980; Box 15
  Framed images of personal documents, and a group picture.
  - Certificate of identification issued to J. Arthur Duff, in Chinese, 1 framed image, undated (Box 15)
  - Certificate of identification #261 issued to Tu-Fu-Yu (J. A. Duff), Special representative of United States Relief, 1943 June 19. (Box 15)
    In Chinese with English translation, 1 framed image. Includes picture of Yu-Hon-Mon, Commander of the Seventh War Zone.
  - Indira Gandhi and J. Arthur Duff with a group of students, group picture, 1 framed image, New Delhi, 1980 March 3. (Box 15)
    With inscription from Indira Gandhi.